RAWAN SAYED ALY

CONTACT INFORMATION:

Location: 6th of October, Giza - Egypt

Email: <u>Email | Gmail.com</u>Phone: +20-1117929376

LinkedIn: <u>Rawan Sayed | LinkedIn</u>
Portfolio: <u>Rawan GitHub | Portfolio</u>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A passionate and skilled front-end web developer with extensive experience in designing and developing responsive and well-designed websites. Having completed several intensive front-end web development bootcamps, I have honed my ability to create professional websites using the latest technologies. My freelance projects have allowed me to explore my passion for web development and continuously challenge myself to deliver high-quality work.

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Electronics and Electrical communications Engineering

Cairo University - Cairo, Egypt

2015 - 2020

GPA: High Good. (73.8%)

High School Sphinx Language School (Grade: 98.9%)

FREELANCE PROJECTS - Portfolio (Code & Live Demos)

Full-Stack Projects:

- Full-Stack Signup/Login Form Mega Project
 - o Developed a comprehensive signup/login form with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, form validation, database integration, and PHP for backend authentication.

React Projects:

- React Shopping Cart
 - o Built a dynamic shopping cart application using React.
- React Pizza Menu
 - o Developed an interactive pizza menu using React, HTML, and CSS.
- React Travel Website
 - o Created a travel website using React.
- Real-Time Chat App
 - o Implemented a real-time chat application with React.
- Educational Website
 - o Designed an educational platform using React.
- React Quiz App
 - o Developed a quiz application using React.
- React Hotel Booking Website
 - o Built a hotel booking website using React.
- React Movie App
 - o Created a movie application using React and integrated with an API.
- React Crypto App
 - o Developed a cryptocurrency tracking app using React and AXIOS for API integration.

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap Projects:

- Coffee Shop Website
 - o Designed and developed a coffee shop website using HTML, CSS, Webstrap, and JavaScript.
- Flower Shop Website

RAWAN SAYED ALY Front-End Dev

- o Created a flower shop website using HTML, CSS, Webstrap, JavaScript, and Bootstrap.
- Grocery Shop Website
 - O Built a grocery shop website using HTML, CSS, Webstrap, JavaScript, and Bootstrap.
- Nature Website
 - o Developed a nature-themed website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- iPhone Demo Website
 - o Created a demo website for an iPhone using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap.

Bootstrap Template

Designed a template using Bootstrap.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Vodafone Egypt | Technical Support Engineer

Mar 2021 - Present

Monitoring network alarms for 5 different domains on MoM, investigation and handling using SecureCRT using Linux commands.

Huawei technologies | Technical Sales Support Engineer (internship)

Dec 2020 - Feb 2021

Installation of BBUs, RRUs, and CPRIs of each site on BOQs. Knowing types of installations and dealing with POs from any customer and translating into site's installation.

SKILLS

Front-End Development:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- EJS (Embedded JavaScript)

Back-End Development:

• Express.js

Tools & Technologies:

- Git
- Postman

RAWAN SAYED ALY Front-End Dev